http://www.bhs.bm/about-bhs/bhs-privacy-notice.html

Search ...
Support BHS - make a donation
About BHSHead Of School WelcomeGuiding StatementsPhilosophyThe Girls AdvantageAccreditationsRound SquareList of StaffBoard of TrusteesBHS Privacy NoticeAcademicsEarly Years Programme PrimaryPhilosophyThe International Primary CurriculumEnglishMathSpecialist SubjectsSecondaryMiddle YearsIGCSE YearsInternational BaccalaureateScholarships & AwardsSchool LifeFirefly at BHSSchool ClubsAfter School CareSports at BHSBHS CalendarUniform GuidelinesStorm / Hurricane PolicyPTAMabel's LabelsCharleston WrapBHS Raffle 2020The Bermuda High School for GirlsThe International Baccalaureate at BHSCOVID-19 InformationAdmissionsFee ScheduleScholarships and Financial AidApplication Forms EYP-Y11Application Forms IBInformation SessionsAlumniOutstanding Service AwardsAlumni AssociationTranscript Request FormSupport BHSLeading the Way Make a Gift OnlineBHS Annual AppealAnnual Appeal FAQsAnnual Appeal 2020-2021Methods of GivingCapital GiftsPlanned GivingIn Memory Donations200 ClubNews/EventsExam Results2020 IB Results2018 IB Results2017 IB Results2016 IB Results2020 GCSE Results2018 I/GCSE Results2017 I/GCSE Results2016 I/GCSE ResultsAnnual ReportsBHS in the NewsSHE LEADS: A real world readiness programmeBHS Written FlameGraduation 2020Holiday Bazaar 2020 - Virtual125 Reasons125 Years of History
BHS Privacy Notice
BHS uses personal information about prospective, current and past: students and their parents/and or guardians; staff; suppliers and contractors; donors, friends and supporters; and other individuals connected to or visiting the School for events, meetings or courses, (including students enrolled in our summer and after school programmes).  We are committed to respecting, and protecting, the privacy of all persons associated with BHS, and to full compliance with the Bermuda Personal Information Protection Act (PIPA), 2016.
This Privacy Notice is intended to provide information about how BHS will use personal information.CLICK HERE TO READ PRIVACY NOTICE
AdminContactStaff WebmailStudent Webmail
© Copyright The Bermuda High School for Girls Association All Rights Reserved.
Telephone: 441.295.6153 Email: info@bhs.bm
